we are young carefree and full of fun
full of energy and hope
we are smiling in the sunshine and
laughing out loud in the rain
ever so eager and adventurous with bold
curiosity and with the impulse to
undertake many ventures and to succeed
in every single one of them
even when it gets real tough at work
nothing seems to be stopping us from
succeeding
but how do we strike a balance between
work and personal life
just like a game of blocks we face risks
with each block we pull out at a time
hoping the stack doesn't fall over
we are actually a lot closer to health
risks than we think
did you know that over 80 percent of the
critical illnesses in malaysia are from
the five common critical illnesses
young malaysians suffer from it too
why not build a strong base from the
very start
get started with a simple and affordable
critical illness plan made just for you
safeguard yourself and your loved ones
with manulife ez5
with an affordable premium this plan
provides you financial coverage from
early to advanced stages of the five
common critical illnesses
as intensive care often comes at a high
cost we will provide you financial
relief in the event of hospitalization
in intensive care unit for a continuous
period of seven days or more
and no matter what your goals in life
are planning ahead is always paramount
when it comes to financial planning
receive guaranteed survival benefit at
the end of every five policy years
lastly provide your family with a lump
sum payment to lessen their financial
burden on bereavement costs
manulife ez5 provides you a simple
solution for your critical illness
coverage needs to make your everyday
better
find out more by visiting our website
calling our customer careline or get in
touch with our professional advisor
today
[Music]